{"surveys":[{"id":1,"name":"NPS","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answers":["1 Not at all likely","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9","10 Highly likley"]}]}},{"id":2,"name":"Employee Satisfaction","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answers":["Very unsatisfied","Unsatisied","Neutral","Satisfied","Very satisfied"]}]}},{"id":3,"name":"Lunch Order","content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answers":["Pizza","Sandwiches","Sushi","Tacos"]}]}}],"responses":[{"id":77747295293,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T21:41:17.187Z"},{"id":707320912578,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},{"id":753380922800,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Pizza"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},{"id":102812084821,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"8"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:07.423Z"},{"id":638202697921,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:17.568Z"},{"id":902644797292,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Unsatisied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:26.191Z"},{"id":277282477605,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"9"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:35.734Z"},{"id":811002305923,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:42.889Z"},{"id":316164475673,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:43:51.380Z"},{"id":576737290613,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:01.438Z"},{"id":195195787901,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Tacos"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:03.204Z"},{"id":122483579918,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:05.559Z"},{"id":542873935938,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:06.227Z"},{"id":854932702841,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:06.816Z"},{"id":389667654359,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:07.291Z"},{"id":662083037378,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:07.467Z"},{"id":503812705295,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:07.620Z"},{"id":912427634035,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:07.790Z"},{"id":185510906421,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Sushi"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T12:44:07.943Z"},{"id":736987528511,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Very satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:47.621Z"},{"id":466566907544,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:49.117Z"},{"id":695191201818,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:49.294Z"},{"id":639706778011,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:49.448Z"},{"id":567231000891,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Very satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:50.533Z"},{"id":651484081613,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Very satisfied"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:50.710Z"},{"id":387138406240,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Neutral"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:52.319Z"},{"id":909526249879,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Neutral"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:52.481Z"},{"id":678660172244,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Neutral"}]},"completed":"2022-10-29T14:26:52.600Z"},{"id":662866501645,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T11:42:17.068Z"},{"id":413702401874,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T11:43:47.782Z"},{"id":695510559870,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"5"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:52.993Z"},{"id":27877195167,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"1 Not at all likely"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:55.703Z"},{"id":399194696510,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:58.197Z"},{"id":120472252260,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:58.520Z"},{"id":5547580100,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:58.714Z"},{"id":477977084869,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:58.882Z"},{"id":198558364943,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:59.050Z"},{"id":775416678766,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-10-30T12:44:59.204Z"}]}
